calvinayre.com 2005-04-04

# Privacy Policy - Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker

Welcome to Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room  
Bodog is an online sports betting and casino gambling entertainment company providing sports betting odds for all major sports, over 50 casino games, and a multi player poker room. If you are viewing this message it is because you are using a web browser that does not support many of the features on this site. Please upgrade your browser to enjoy the full range of online betting options that Bodog has to offer." 

Any private information received by Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room WILL NOT be given out to anyone or any organization; it WILL NEVER be sold or distributed in any form, or for any purpose unless approved by the account holder. Therefore, client information collected by Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room is the property of Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room and is not shared with any third party, including merchants. 

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room is dedicated to providing useful, relevant and valuable information to our customers and subscribers. To do this, we offer an assortment of ongoing, daily, weekly and monthly publications. By opting in to receiving email from Bodog.com a client is automatically subscribed to the following publications: 

Bodog Newsletter - Weekly   
The latest sports and poker updates, plus Bodog's newest props and more. 

Bodog 5th Street Poker Newsletter - Biweekly   
Breaking poker news, useful poker tips and strategies.

Special Promotional Offers - Ongoing   
Information and/or offers on any new Bodog Sportsbook, Racebook, Casino or Poker Room merchandise, bonus, promotion, or event. 

Service Announcements - As Needed   
Important messages concerning any temporary site or system outages, plus any maintenance issues that may affect the level of service. 

To assure the quality of client communications, Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room provides clients with the opportunity to view or modify their subscription preferences at any time simply by logging in to their account and selecting "Manage Subscriptions" from the "My Account" screen. 

If a client chooses to opt-out of receiving email from Bodog.com there is, however, a certain minimum level of communication needed for a client to play effectively, so everyone with a Bodog account will receive a "Welcome" email, containing valuable account information, and "Service Announcements". 

If at any time a client wishes to indicate that they never want to receive communications from us, or if they wish to change or correct any previously provided information, they can also email us with the request at [service@bodog.com](mailto:service@bodog.com) or call toll-free at 1-888-263-0000. 

Qualified Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room staff have access to account numbers, account holder names, telephone numbers, addresses, and email addresses and in some cases passwords. Clients can change their password directly on the Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room web site (under "My Account/Change Password"). 

If a client needs to change their address, email address and/or telephone number, they should submit their changes directly from the Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room web site (under "My Account/Change Address"). New information will be verified with card-issuing banks and updated accordingly. Clients must ensure that card-issuing banks have their new address and phone number PRIOR to submitting their Profile Updates. 

A client who loses their account login information may retrieve it via "Forgot your account number?" or "Forgot your password?" found in the "My Account" screens of the Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room web site, or by clicking on the relevant FAQ in the Help section. All changes made to account holder information, whether done online or by telephone, are logged. It is Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room policy not to change an account holder's name unless we have an official name change notification on file (e.g. marriage certificate, notice of name change). 

If an individual becomes aware that personal information we maintain about that individual is inaccurate, or if an individual would like to update or review his or her personal information, the individual may contact us using the contact information below. As a security precaution, we may request that the individual provide identifying information such as name, address, birth date, etc. In addition, we may limit or deny access to personal information where providing such access would be unreasonably burdensome or expensive in the circumstances, or as otherwise permitted by the Safe Harbor Agreement. 

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room use cookies to track how and when customers use the site. (NB: Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make web surfing easier by saving your passwords and other preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find cookies at most major web sites). Cookies also help us to see which areas of the site are popular and which are not. We can then improve the site based on this information. 

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room also log IP addresses for system administration purposes. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your wagering account. Bodog download products also record a unique computer ID. 

The Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room website contains links to other sites; we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker Room will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. Bodog will obtain your opt-in consent for any updates to this Privacy Policy that materially expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Policy at the time of collection. 

**Contact Information**

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail message to: [service@bodog.com](mailto:service@bodog.com). You can also contact Bodog at:

Bodog Sportsbook, Casino and Poker   
Oficentro Sabana Sur  
San Jose, Costa Rica  
International Phone: 506-296-6338  
North American Phone: 1-888-263-0000 

Last Updated: February 2005
